https://www.faygo.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY
Faygo®
Website Privacy Policy
General
Faygo Beverages, Inc., a National Beverage company, (“Faygo”), respects the privacy of every individual who visits our Faygo® website at www.faygo.com (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy outlines the information Faygo may collect on our Site and how we may use that information.
Personal Data
All “personal information” (“personal information” is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. Faygo reserves the right to change the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy at any time. You agree to review these terms and conditions periodically to become aware of any such changes. Your continued use of the Site shall be deemed your acceptance of any changed terms and conditions.
Faygo will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or email address) through our Site unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. Please do not submit personal data to us if you do not want it collected. If you do provide us with personal data, we may use that information in the following ways (unless stated otherwise): we may provide you with information about Faygo or its products on a regular basis; we may store and process your information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services; we (or a fulfillment house or other third party on our behalf in connection with a promotion) may use that information to contact you; and/or we may provide other third parties with aggregate – but not individual – information about visitors to or users of our sites. We do not now and do not intend to sell, rent or market personal data about you to third parties.
Your choices with respect to personal information
Faygo recognizes and appreciates the importance of the responsible use of information collected on the Site. Without your consent, Faygo will not communicate any information to you regarding products, services and special offers available from Faygo, although we may find it necessary to communicate with you regarding your use of the services on this Site. Except in the particular circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, Faygo will also not provide your name to other companies or organizations without your consent.
There are other instances in which Faygo may divulge your personal information. Faygo may provide your personal information if necessary and in Faygo’s good faith judgment to comply with laws or regulations of a governmental or regulatory body or in response to a valid subpoena, warrant or order or to protect the rights of Faygo or others.
Also, please note that Faygo is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other third party websites to which the Site or any other third party website may link. You should review the privacy policy of such sites before using the sites.
Additional Information Collected Automatically
When you use the Site, Faygo or third parties authorized by Faygo may also collect certain technical and routing information about your computer to facilitate your use of the Site and its services. For example, we may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer. We may use these environmental variables to facilitate and track your use of the Site and its services. Faygo also may use such environmental variables to measure traffic patterns on the Site. Without expressly informing you in each particular circumstance, we do not match such information with any of your personal information.
Faygo may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. Faygo may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing or similar promotional purposes.
Use of Cookies
When you view the Site, Faygo may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “Cookie” or similar file and can help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor a website to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
Use of IP addresses
Faygo may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information such as the number of visitors from a geographic area.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site or your dealings with it, you may e-mail us at legalnotice@faygo.com.
That warm fuzzy feeling delivered to you in liquid form with no calories.
Drinking this diet grapefruit-cherry pop feels like floating in water of the perfect temperature.
Drinking this grapefruit-cherry pop is much like cooling down from the heat while simultaneously warming up from the cold.
Now you can drink into the night without the worry of calories creeping in.
The most underappreciated late-night flavor.
Not all lemon-lime drinks need to kick you in the taste buds to be delicious. This is proof.
It’s not the same as orange juice, but that doesn’t mean you can’t drink it in the morning.
Grapefruit was just begging to be made into a sparkling drink, so we listened.
All the taste of cherries without the stems.
Buy Now
Find In Store
×
